(Watch on www.kisskh.xyz Support Admin)
(شاهد على www.kisskh.xyz دعم الإدارة)
huh?
هاه؟
The fuck? Who the hell are you?
ما هذا بحق الجحيم؟ من أنت بحق الجحيم؟
Come on. Come on, you son of a bitch.
هيا. هيا يا ابن العاهرة.
Asshole!
الأحمق!
Fuck this shit.
تباً لهذا الهراء.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Oh…
أوه…
Bro, we gotta call an ambulance.
يا أخي، يجب أن نتصل بالإسعاف.
That's a bad idea, Gun-woo.
هذه فكرة سيئة يا غون وو.
Dude, this guy is dying.
يا رجل، هذا الشخص يحتضر.
Uh, Hyeon-ju,
أوه، هيون جو،
a homeless old man was injured really badly,
أصيب رجل عجوز بلا مأوى بجروح بالغة.
so we called an ambulance.
لذلك اتصلنا بالإسعاف.
- What about Yang Jae-myeong? - Uh, he ran away.
- ماذا عن يانغ جاي ميونغ؟ - آه، لقد هرب.
Goddammit! I told you not to get involved.
اللعنة! لقد قلت لك ألا تتدخل.
I mean, he was really badly hurt.
أعني، لقد أصيب بجروح بالغة.
We had no choice.
لم يكن لدينا خيار آخر.
You don't even know the guy, so why would you interfere? Damn it!
أنت لا تعرف الرجل حتى، فلماذا تتدخل؟ اللعنة!
Uh, I know, but we--
أجل، أعرف، لكننا...
So what should we do?
إذن، ما الذي ينبغي علينا فعله؟
I'll give her a call.
سأتصل بها.
What?
ماذا؟
Yes, Hyeon-ju, uh, about this… We are really, really sorry.
نعم، هيون جو، بخصوص هذا الأمر... نحن آسفون للغاية.
This was totally our fault 100 times over.
كان هذا خطأنا بالكامل، مئة مرة.
Where are you right now? Just let me apologize to you in person.
أين أنت الآن؟ دعني أعتذر لك شخصياً.
Forget it. It's over.
انسَ الأمر. لقد انتهى.
Please, Hyeon-ju, just give us five minutes.
من فضلك يا هيون جو، امنحنا خمس دقائق فقط.
We just… feel really badly, and I'm sorry about the whole thing.
نشعر بالسوء الشديد، وأنا آسف بشأن كل ما حدث.
Gun-woo also wants to apologize.
يريد غون وو أيضاً الاعتذار.
- Please, just give us five minutes. -
- من فضلك، امنحنا خمس دقائق فقط. -
Come on.
تعال.
Meet me at the bookstore.
قابلني في المكتبة.
Dude, look…
يا رجل، انظر...
To be honest with you, I really don't get it.
لأكون صريحاً معك، أنا حقاً لا أفهم الأمر.
What don't you get, huh?
ما الذي لا تفهمه، هاه؟
I mean, if we didn't do anything to help him,
أعني، لو لم نفعل أي شيء لمساعدته،
that old man would've definitely died.
كان ذلك الرجل العجوز سيموت بالتأكيد.
You saw it yourself.
لقد رأيت ذلك بنفسك.
I did.
فعلتُ.
So if saving that man was the right thing,
إذاً، إذا كان إنقاذ ذلك الرجل هو الشيء الصحيح،
why did you have to apologize for what we did?
لماذا كان عليك الاعتذار عما فعلناه؟
- Why do we have to say we're sorry? - This was our first time on the job.
- لماذا علينا أن نقول إننا آسفون؟ -  كانت هذه أول مرة لنا في العمل.
Hyeon-ju wasn't there, so it's hard for her to understand what happened.
لم تكن هيون جو موجودة، لذا يصعب عليها فهم ما حدث.
She's still learning how we respond.
لا تزال تتعلم كيف نستجيب.
That's why she got mad when things didn't go as planned,
ولهذا السبب غضبت عندما لم تسر الأمور كما هو مخطط لها،
but if we apologize and take the blame, I think she'll be cool,
لكن إذا اعتذرنا وتحملنا المسؤولية، أعتقد أنها ستتقبل الأمر.
and at the end, hopefully she'll trust us more.
وفي النهاية، نأمل أن تثق بنا أكثر.
- But… - Gun-woo.
- لكن... - غون وو.
I know you didn't do anything wrong. I was right there with you.
أعلم أنك لم تفعل أي شيء خاطئ. كنتُ بجانبك تماماً.
But thinking about it as a job,
لكن التفكير في الأمر كوظيفة،
a new job with a new boss, we should try to smooth it over.
وظيفة جديدة مع رئيس جديد، يجب أن نحاول تسهيل الأمور.
Just this once, okay?
هذه المرة فقط، حسناً؟
Yeah, okay.
حسناً، لا بأس.
BLOODHOUNDS
كلاب الصيد
Don't sit. This won't take long.
لا تجلس. لن يستغرق الأمر وقتاً طويلاً.
You fought Yang Jae-myeong, didn't you?
لقد قاتلت يانغ جاي ميونغ، أليس كذلك؟
We had no choice, so… so yeah.
لم يكن لدينا خيار، لذا... أجل.
We can't work together anymore.
لم يعد بإمكاننا العمل معاً.
What? Isn't it obvious?
ماذا؟ أليس الأمر واضحاً؟
I mean, we said we were sorry.
أعني، لقد قلنا إننا آسفون.
I don't need an apology!
لست بحاجة إلى اعتذار!
Yang Jae-myeong saw your faces, didn't he?
رأى يانغ جاي ميونغ وجوهكم، أليس كذلك؟
My plan was to quietly tail him…
كانت خطتي هي أن أتعقبه بهدوء...
…and gather evidence,
...وجمع الأدلة،
but now that he knows someone's on to him, he'll probably lie low,
لكن الآن وقد علم أن أحدهم قد كشف أمره، فمن المرجح أنه سيلتزم الصمت.
and who knows for long.
ومن يدري إلى متى سيستمر ذلك.
So, because of you, my plan is ruined.
لذا، بسببك، فسدت خطتي.
We wore caps and masks. He couldn't have seen our faces.
كنا نرتدي قبعات وأقنعة. لم يكن بإمكانه رؤية وجوهنا.
Oh! You covered your face then there's no way he can recognize you.
أوه! لقد غطيت وجهك، إذن لا يمكنه التعرف عليك بأي حال من الأحوال.
Since this shitty hair was covered up, you have an amazing disguise.
بما أن هذا الشعر السيئ كان مغطى، فلديك تنكر رائع.
Goddammit! I would recognize you from a mile away!
يا إلهي! سأتعرف عليك من على بعد ميل!
Well? Get out.
حسناً؟ اخرج.
- We apologized. - I said get out!
- اعتذرنا. - قلتُ اخرج!
- We had no choice given the situation. - What situation?
- لم يكن لدينا خيار آخر نظراً للوضع. - أي وضع؟
It's our first time working together.
هذه أول مرة نعمل فيها معاً.
- You can't expect perfection. - That's why I refused you!
لا يمكنك أن تتوقع الكمال. - لهذا السبب رفضتك!
- We did what we thought was right. - What situation warrants that?
- فعلنا ما اعتقدنا أنه الصواب. - ما هو الموقف الذي يبرر ذلك؟
- I told you earlier. - Do you not hear me?
- لقد أخبرتك سابقاً. - ألا تسمعني؟
- What does my hair have to do with it? - We'll go. We'll go.
- ما علاقة شعري بالموضوع؟ - سنذهب. سنذهب.
We'll leave right now, so please stop shouting.
سنغادر الآن، لذا من فضلك توقف عن الصراخ.
I will find a way to return
سأجد طريقة للعودة
the hundred million that Mr. Choi gave me.
المئة مليون التي أعطاني إياها السيد تشوي.
But… since Woo-jin and I just listened to you yelling at us,
لكن... بما أنني ووو-جين استمعنا للتو إلى صراخك علينا،
please listen to one thing I have to say.
أرجوكم استمعوا إلى شيء واحد أريد قوله.
If someone offered to make your work go smoothly
إذا عرض عليك أحدهم تسهيل عملك
in exchange for killing someone,
مقابل قتل شخص ما،
could you do it?
هل يمكنك فعل ذلك؟
That boss of Smile Capital did this to my face.
لقد فعل رئيس شركة سمايل كابيتال هذا بي وجهاً لوجه.
If I had done nothing when a man was dying in front of me,
لو لم أفعل شيئاً عندما كان رجل يحتضر أمامي،
then don't you think I'd be even worse than that guy.
إذن ألا تعتقد أنني سأكون أسوأ من ذلك الرجل؟
It would have been wrong.
كان ذلك خطأً.
Please just think about it.
أرجوك فكر في الأمر.
I'll find something else.
سأبحث عن شيء آخر.
Don't worry too much.
لا تقلق كثيراً.
I'm sorry. I couldn't hold myself back.
أنا آسف. لم أستطع كبح جماح نفسي.
You held back better than I did.
لقد كبحتَ جماحك بشكل أفضل مني.
You hungry? I know this 24-hour soup place. Let's go.
هل أنت جائع؟ أعرف مطعم شوربة مفتوح 24 ساعة. هيا بنا.
Wait.
انتظر.
It's probably closed because of COVID. It's past ten.
ربما يكون مغلقاً بسبب كوفيد-19. لقد تجاوزت الساعة العاشرة.
Well that just made me hungry for nothing.
حسناً، هذا جعلني أشعر بالجوع بلا سبب.
I forgot.
لقد نسيت.
My stomach hurts.
معدتي تؤلمني.
Hey, it isn't my fault they're closed because of COVID.
يا رجل، ليس ذنبي أنهم مغلقون بسبب كوفيد.
Well, it is your fault for bringing it up.
حسناً، أنت المخطئ لأنك أثرت هذا الموضوع.
Hey, you also couldn't hold yourself back with her.
مهلاً، أنت أيضاً لم تستطع كبح جماح نفسك معها.
You just said I did a good job holding back.
لقد قلت للتو أنني قمت بعمل جيد في ضبط النفس.
I only said it because I felt bad.
قلت ذلك فقط لأنني شعرت بالسوء.
- You were moping like a goddamn loser. - I wasn't moping like a goddamn loser.
- كنتَ مكتئباً كخاسرٍ حقير. - لم أكن مكتئباً كخاسرٍ حقير.
"I wasn't moping like a goddamn loser."
"لم أكن أبكي كخاسرٍ حقير."
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'm imitating you, you loser. "God, I'm hungry."
أنا أقلدك أيها الخاسر. "يا إلهي، أنا جائع."
- "Oh, my stomach hurts." - Wow.
- "أوه، معدتي تؤلمني." - يا إلهي.
Dude, that's pretty harsh.
يا رجل، هذا قاسٍ جداً.
You can't even take a joke now?
ألا تستطيع حتى تقبل المزاح الآن؟
Huh? You weren't joking. That was totally serious.
هاه؟ لم تكن تمزح. كان الأمر جديًا تمامًا.
Hey, I'm seriously offended. Apologize to me.
يا إلهي، لقد شعرتُ بإهانة بالغة. أرجو منك الاعتذار لي.
SORRY, I WAS WRONG. SEE YOU AT THE OFFICE TOMORROW AT 10:00 A.M.
معذرةً، كنت مخطئاً. أراك في المكتب غداً الساعة العاشرة صباحاً.
I knew this would happen.
كنت أعرف أن هذا سيحدث.
Yeah! It's short. It's short. It's short.
أجل! إنه قصير. إنه قصير. إنه قصير.
- Super short. - Super short!
- قصير جداً. - قصير جداً!
- Fuck! Will you shut the fuck up? - Get out of here, loser.
- اللعنة! هل ستصمت بحق الجحيم؟ - اخرج من هنا أيها الخاسر.
- "Will you shut the fuck up?" - Why are you mad? It's just a game.
- "هل ستصمت بحق الجحيم؟" - لماذا أنت غاضب؟ إنها مجرد لعبة.
- Calm down. - It's your turn. Go!
- اهدأ. - حان دورك. انطلق!
- Watch it. - Okay, I will.
- شاهدها. - حسناً، سأفعل.
- Your turn. - Fuck off.
- دورك. - اذهب إلى الجحيم.
YANG JAE-MYEONG I'M WAITING IN FRONT OF THE GOLF SHOP
يانغ جاي ميونغ، أنا أنتظر أمام متجر لوازم الغولف
Stop swearing.
توقف عن الشتم.
- You have to wear your mask, sir. - Sure thing.
- عليك ارتداء الكمامة يا سيدي. - بالتأكيد.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Sir, someone was following us.
سيدي، كان أحدهم يتبعنا.
Who was it?
من كان؟
They were young, but they seemed to know how to fight.
كانوا صغاراً في السن، لكن يبدو أنهم كانوا يعرفون كيف يقاتلون.
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
Huh?
هاه؟
You sure someone was following you, you idiot?!
هل أنت متأكد من أن أحدهم كان يتبعك أيها الأحمق؟!
Focus.
ركز.
Uh, the thing is…
آه، الأمر هو...
Talk.
يتحدث.
Before I started working for you, sir,
قبل أن أبدأ العمل لديك يا سيدي،
I sort of borrowed money from a place.
لقد اقترضت المال من مكان ما.
The fuckers didn't say anything, so I just ignored them.
لم ينطق هؤلاء الأوغاد بأي كلمة، لذلك تجاهلتهم ببساطة.
Talk faster.
تحدث بسرعة أكبر.
But those guys came for the money recently.
لكن هؤلاء الرجال جاؤوا مؤخراً من أجل المال.
The bastard that came over was wearing a hat with a red cat on it.
ذلك الوغد الذي جاء كان يرتدي قبعة عليها صورة قطة حمراء.
And one of the punks who jumped us was wearing the same hat.
وكان أحد هؤلاء المراهقين المشاغبين الذين اعتدوا علينا يرتدي نفس القبعة.
You sure it's him?
هل أنت متأكد أنه هو؟
It was the same hat, sir.
كانت نفس القبعة يا سيدي.
Where did you borrow the money from?
من أين اقترضت المال؟
So basically, this is what happened yesterday.
باختصار، هذا ما حدث بالأمس.
Yang Jae-myeong had already robbed that homeless man of his ID,
كان يانغ جاي ميونغ قد سرق بالفعل هوية ذلك الرجل المشرد،
but he had forgotten,
لكنه نسي،
and he tried to con him again, which ended up in a fight.
وحاول خداعه مرة أخرى، الأمر الذي انتهى بشجار.
Uh, but just how much money
لكن كم من المال تحديداً؟
do Jae-myeong's guys borrow with one stolen ID?
هل يقترض رجال جاي ميونغ باستخدام هوية مسروقة واحدة؟
About 50 million won per fake account.
حوالي 50 مليون وون لكل حساب مزيف.
That's 500 million for ten IDs.
هذا يعني 500 مليون مقابل عشرة هويات.
Jesus. How long have they been doing this?
يا إلهي. منذ متى وهم يفعلون هذا؟
I think at least for half a year, yeah.
أعتقد أن ذلك سيستمر لنصف عام على الأقل، نعم.
Wow! They must have made a small fortune.
يا للعجب! لا بد أنهم جنوا ثروة طائلة.
Hm.
همم.
But those loan sharks that they conned, did they just sit back and do nothing?
لكن هل جلس أولئك المرابون الذين خدعوهم ولم يفعلوا شيئاً؟
If they call the cops, they'll be investigated,
إذا اتصلوا بالشرطة، فسيتم التحقيق معهم.
so that's not an option.
لذا فهذا ليس خياراً مطروحاً.
My take is they're trying to recover the money on their own but can't.
أعتقد أنهم يحاولون استرداد الأموال بأنفسهم لكنهم لا يستطيعون.
This is my plan.
هذه هي خطتي.
Find the private loan sharks that Yang Jae-myeong conned,
ابحث عن مُقرضي القروض الخاصين الذين احتال عليهم يانغ جاي ميونغ،
and then we recover the money he stole for a commission.
ثم نسترد الأموال التي سرقها كعمولة.
With a 1% commission, we would get three billion won.
بعمولة قدرها 1%، سنحصل على ثلاثة مليارات وون.
We should at least charge 2%.
ينبغي أن نفرض رسوماً لا تقل عن 2%.
Hyung?
هيونغ؟
If loan sharks get conned,
إذا تعرض المرابون للاحتيال،
wouldn't that make things worse for the people who got loans from them?
ألن يؤدي ذلك إلى تفاقم الأمور بالنسبة للأشخاص الذين حصلوا على قروض منهم؟
Huh?
هاه؟
They might end up torturing their clients in order to get their money back.
قد ينتهي بهم الأمر إلى تعذيب عملائهم من أجل استعادة أموالهم.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
It's just… I think small business owners are the ones that will suffer the most.
الأمر ببساطة... أعتقد أن أصحاب المشاريع الصغيرة هم الأكثر تضرراً.
You're right about that.
أنت محق في ذلك.
Mm.
مم.
How did they find us?
كيف عثروا علينا؟
How did they find us?!
كيف عثروا علينا؟!
I… I don't know.
أنا... لا أعرف.
Turn off the lights and the sign outside.
أطفئ الأنوار واللافتة الموجودة بالخارج.
Damn it!
عليك اللعنة!
PYEONGHWA BOOKS
كتب بيونغهوا
- Turn your phones off for now. - Okay.
- أغلقوا هواتفكم الآن. - حسناً.
- It's here? Are you sure? - Yes. I'm sure, sir.
- هل هو هنا؟ هل أنت متأكد؟ - نعم، أنا متأكد يا سيدي.
You borrowed money from a bookstore?
هل اقترضت مالاً من مكتبة؟
Yeah, the owner here used to be a big moneylender back in the day.
نعم، كان صاحب هذا المكان في الماضي مُقرضاً كبيراً للأموال.
Hey, give this a kick here.
هيا، أعطِ هذا دفعة هنا.
Try this.
جرب هذا.
Come on. Hurry up, you idiot.
هيا، أسرع أيها الأحمق.
Ow.
آخ.
- Kick harder. - Huh?
- اركل بقوة أكبر. - هاه؟
Kick harder, you asshole!
اركل بقوة أكبر أيها الوغد!
Uh…
أوه…
Harder!
أصعب!
Kick fucking harder!
اركل بقوة أكبر!
Stop. That's enough.
توقف. هذا يكفي.
We'll need something stronger to tear this down.
سنحتاج إلى شيء أقوى لهدم هذا.
This here is the safe.
هذا هو الخزنة.
Last night on your way back, did you check if you were being followed?
هل تحققت الليلة الماضية في طريق عودتك مما إذا كان أحد يتبعك؟
Uh, well, we took the bus.
حسنًا، لقد استقلينا الحافلة.
You realize they could have followed the bus.
تدرك أنهم كان بإمكانهم اللحاق بالحافلة.
If they had followed us last night, why didn't they jump us right away?
إذا كانوا قد تبعونا الليلة الماضية، فلماذا لم يهاجمونا على الفور؟
Why decide to make their move now?
لماذا قرروا القيام بهذه الخطوة الآن؟
- He might've wanted to bring Kim Jun-min-- - Whoa, no, Hyeon-ju.
- ربما كان يريد إحضار كيم جون مين - - مهلاً، لا، هيون جو.
Yang Jae-myeong saw how we fought last night.
لقد رأى يانغ جاي ميونغ كيف تقاتلنا الليلة الماضية.
If he was planning on jumping us, he would've brought more muscle.
لو كان يخطط لمهاجمتنا، لكان قد أحضر معه المزيد من الرجال.
I bet… they weren't sure.
أراهن أنهم لم يكونوا متأكدين.
But now, they might have caught onto something.
لكن الآن، ربما يكونون قد أدركوا شيئاً ما.
In any case, we need to figure out how they found out about this place.
على أي حال، نحن بحاجة إلى معرفة كيف علموا بهذا المكان.
That's how we don't make the same mistake twice
هكذا نتجنب تكرار نفس الخطأ مرتين
Okay. That's a good idea.
حسناً. هذه فكرة جيدة.
Why don't we sit down and talk it through, hm?
لماذا لا نجلس ونتحدث في الأمر، همم؟
Hm.
همم.
Does Yang Jae-myeong know about this place?
هل يعرف يانغ جاي ميونغ عن هذا المكان؟
He came here a long time ago.
لقد جاء إلى هنا منذ زمن بعيد.
That means he's caught onto our connection here somehow.
هذا يعني أنه قد أدرك وجود صلة بيننا بطريقة ما.
- Oh! - Huh?
- أوه! - هاه؟
Oh!
أوه!
Uh…
أوه…
Hyeon-ju, I think he may have recognized your cap.
هيون جو، أعتقد أنه ربما يكون قد تعرف على قبعتك.
The thing is,
المسألة هي،
I followed you a while back
لقد تابعتك منذ فترة
when I saw you chasing down a homeless man.
عندما رأيتك تطارد رجلاً بلا مأوى.
Wait…
انتظر…
Yeah, that was me.
نعم، كنت أنا.
The homeless man back then was Yang Jae-myeong.
كان الرجل المشرد آنذاك هو يانغ جاي ميونغ.
Oh, wow.
يا للعجب!
Uh… I was wearing that cap back then, wasn't I?
آه... كنت أرتدي تلك القبعة حينها، أليس كذلك؟
Uh, yes, I definitely remember seeing it on you.
أجل، أتذكر بالتأكيد أنني رأيته عليك.
Then that might've been how they found out.
إذن ربما كانت هذه هي الطريقة التي اكتشفوا بها الأمر.
Okay, but why do you think they kicked the shutters.
حسناً، لكن لماذا تعتقد أنهم ركلوا الستائر؟
Our shutters were custom-made with steel, not aluminum.
صُنعت مصاريعنا خصيصاً من الفولاذ، وليس من الألومنيوم.
I think they were checking for that.
أعتقد أنهم كانوا يتحققون من ذلك.
I think they'll be back.
أعتقد أنهم سيعودون.
Why is he here?
لماذا هو هنا؟
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
What have you done?
ماذا فعلت؟
That white car came here, didn't it?
ألم تأتِ تلك السيارة البيضاء إلى هنا؟
Are you not going to talk?
ألن تتحدث؟
I am sorry, sir. It's entirely my fault.
أنا آسف يا سيدي. إنه خطأي بالكامل.
The two of us… We went on a job last night.
نحن الاثنان... ذهبنا في مهمة الليلة الماضية.
What job?
ما هي الوظيفة؟
Uh, the thing is…
آه، الأمر هو...
What job was that?
ما هي تلك الوظيفة؟
We were tailing Yang Jae-myeong.
كنا نلاحق يانغ جاي ميونغ.
- Why? - Grandpa.
- لماذا؟ - جدي.
Loan sharks are desperate to catch Yang Jae-myeong.
يسعى المرابون بشدة للإيقاع بيانغ جاي ميونغ.
I'm sure they'll be willing to pay for it.
أنا متأكد من أنهم سيكونون على استعداد لدفع ثمنه.
And I believe I'm the only one who is able to catch him.
وأعتقد أنني الوحيد القادر على الإمساك به.
Are you doing this to make money?
هل تفعل هذا لكسب المال؟
It's good to make money.
من الجيد كسب المال.
And what did you guys do?
وماذا فعلتم أنتم؟
It's my… friends' job to protect me, right?
أليس من واجب أصدقائي حمايتي؟
Well, they did.
حسناً، لقد فعلوا ذلك.
I'm disappointed in you.
أشعر بخيبة أمل تجاهك.
Yeah, well, I'm disappointed in you too, Grandpa.
أجل، حسناً، أنا أيضاً أشعر بخيبة أمل منك يا جدي.
It's clear Yang Jae-myeong is up to no good,
من الواضح أن يانغ جاي ميونغ يخطط لشيء سيء.
so why aren't you doing anything?
فلماذا لا تفعل أي شيء؟
With your orders, Mr. Hwang could get rid of a loser like him immediately.
بأوامرك، يستطيع السيد هوانغ التخلص من خاسر مثله على الفور.
So you're frustrated? Well, I'm even more frustrated!
إذن أنت محبط؟ حسنًا، أنا أكثر إحباطًا!
Go ahead. Take off that bandage on your face.
تفضل. انزع تلك الضمادة عن وجهك.
- Hm? - Hurry up and do it.
- همم؟ - أسرع وافعلها.
If Yang Jae-myeong and Kim Jun-min keep scamming private loan sharks,
إذا استمر يانغ جاي ميونغ وكيم جون مين في الاحتيال على مُقرضي القروض الخاصة،
they'll keep threatening and harassing powerless people like Gun-woo here.
سيستمرون في تهديد ومضايقة الأشخاص العاجزين مثل غون وو هنا.
That's going to make all the charity work you do meaningless.
هذا سيجعل كل أعمالك الخيرية بلا معنى.
Your money will go straight into their pockets!
ستذهب أموالك مباشرة إلى جيوبهم!
If you really want to help out those in need,
إذا كنت ترغب حقاً في مساعدة المحتاجين،
you should weed out the punks like Yang Jae-myeong first.
يجب عليك أولاً التخلص من أمثال يانغ جاي ميونغ، وهم من أمثال هؤلاء المنحرفين.
Who did that to Gun-woo's face?
من فعل ذلك بوجه غون وو؟
The boss of Smile Capital did it, sir.
لقد فعلها رئيس شركة سمايل كابيتال يا سيدي.
And his name?
وما اسمه؟
Uh, well, I don't know his name, sir.
حسنًا، لا أعرف اسمه يا سيدي.
But he had a long knife scar running down his left cheek.
لكن كان لديه ندبة سكين طويلة تمتد على خده الأيسر.
You guys head back now.
عودوا الآن.
Sir, could it just be a coincidence?
سيدي، هل يمكن أن يكون الأمر مجرد صدفة؟
Please check whether Kim Myeong-gil is the CEO of Smile Capital.
يرجى التحقق مما إذا كان كيم ميونغ غيل هو الرئيس التنفيذي لشركة سمايل كابيتال.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Juju.
جوجو.
- Getting too comfortable, aren't we? - I mean, you called us friends before.
- هل أصبحنا مرتاحين أكثر من اللازم؟ - أعني، لقد وصفتنا بالأصدقاء من قبل.
I have to say, that felt good.
لا بد لي من القول، لقد كان شعوراً جيداً.
So?
لذا؟
So I thought it might be nice to talk more casually with each other.
لذلك فكرت أنه قد يكون من الجيد أن نتحدث مع بعضنا البعض بشكل أكثر عفوية.
We are a team, after all, Juju.
نحن فريق واحد في النهاية يا جوجو.
Hm, we're not a team if we don't speak casually?
همم، لن نكون فريقاً إذا لم نتحدث بشكل عفوي؟
I'm just saying it would be nice
أقول فقط إنه سيكون أمراً لطيفاً
if we acted more like one big happy family.
لو تصرفنا أكثر كعائلة واحدة كبيرة سعيدة.
It's just a suggestion.
إنها مجرد اقتراح.
Well, if we're family, the oldest would treat the rest to a meal.
حسناً، إذا كنا عائلة، فسيتكفل الأكبر سناً بدعوة البقية لتناول وجبة.
So will you be buying?
هل ستشتري؟
Uh, I actually prefer formalities, ma'am.
في الحقيقة، أنا أفضل الإجراءات الرسمية يا سيدتي.
I'm kidding. Relax.
أمزح. اهدأ.
Let's use Grandpa's credit card. What do you guys want?
لنستخدم بطاقة ائتمان جدي. ماذا تريدون يا رفاق؟
Rib eye.
ريب آي.
Then you pay.
ثم تدفع.
Uh, barbecue buffet.
آه، بوفيه شواء.
- A barbecue buffet? - Yeah, I know a really great place.
- بوفيه شواء؟ - نعم، أعرف مكاناً رائعاً حقاً.
Mm, sure.
مم، بالتأكيد.
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
How long have you been friends with Gun-woo?
منذ متى وأنت صديق لجون وو؟
I don't think it really matters how long you've known a person.
لا أعتقد أن مدة معرفتك بشخص ما مهمة حقاً.
Just knowing someone for a while doesn't mean they're your friend.
مجرد معرفة شخص ما لفترة من الوقت لا يعني أنه صديقك.
Okay.
تمام.
What really matters is how similar your life trajectories have been.
الأمر المهم حقاً هو مدى تشابه مسارات حياتكم.
So even if it's a short conversation,
حتى لو كانت محادثة قصيرة،
you gain a deep understanding of each other.
تكتسبون فهماً عميقاً لبعضكم البعض.
That's what matters.
هذا هو المهم.
- That's the relationship you guys have? - Right.
- هذه هي العلاقة التي تربطكما؟ - صحيح.
It's like we're boxers,
الأمر أشبه بأننا ملاكمون،
but we exchange a lot more than just our fists. Pow!
لكننا نتبادل أكثر بكثير من مجرد قبضاتنا. بوووم!
"So that's the kind of life you've lived."
"إذن هذا هو نوع الحياة التي عشتها."
Pow!
بوووم!
"Well, this is how I lived, you punk."
"حسنًا، هكذا عشتُ، أيها الوغد."
Each blow contains both fighters' character, heart,
كل ضربة تحمل في طياتها شخصية كلا المقاتلين وقلبهما.
history, history,
التاريخ، التاريخ،
History?
تاريخ؟
History.
تاريخ.
We see it all.
نحن نرى كل شيء.
We know. Mm.
نعلم ذلك. مم.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
And besides, Gun-woo is…
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، فإن غون وو هو...
a senior Marine.
ضابط كبير في مشاة البحرية.
And that tells you everything.
وهذا يوضح لك كل شيء.
What exactly does it tell you?
ماذا يخبرك هذا بالضبط؟
Everything.
كل شئ.
Everything about what?
كل شيء عن ماذا؟
Juju, this isn't something I just can't easily explain to you.
جوجو، هذا ليس شيئاً لا أستطيع شرحه لك بسهولة.
It's just, you know, a Marine thing.
إنها مجرد عادة خاصة بسلاح مشاة البحرية، كما تعلمون.
It's like when rappers use hip-hop as an all-encompassing term
يشبه الأمر استخدام مغني الراب مصطلح "الهيب هوب" كمصطلح شامل.
when they look at something and go, "This is hip-hop."
عندما ينظرون إلى شيء ما ويقولون: "هذا هو الهيب هوب".
It's indescribable.
لا يمكن وصفه.
Oh, indescribable, you say?
أوه، لا يمكن وصفه، كما تقول؟
- Are you being sarcastic? - Who? Me?
- هل أنت ساخر؟ - من؟ أنا؟
Hey, this stuff is really…
يا إلهي، هذا الشيء حقاً...
- Here we go. - Right.
- هيا بنا. - حسناً.
Huh?
هاه؟
Dude, you haven't turned on the grill yet?
يا رجل، ألم تقم بتشغيل الشواية بعد؟
You didn't tell me to.
أنت لم تطلب مني ذلك.
Come on, man. Whoever is sitting down is supposed to get the grill going.
هيا يا رجل. من المفترض أن يقوم من يجلس بإشعال الشواية.
I didn't know that. Why didn't you turn it when we got here?
لم أكن أعرف ذلك. لماذا لم تقم بتدويره عندما وصلنا إلى هنا؟
Because the grill would've burned up in the time it took to return with meat.
لأن الشواية كانت ستحترق في الوقت الذي استغرقه العودة باللحم.
How would a grill burn up?
كيف يمكن أن تحترق الشواية؟
Well, technically, the grill itself doesn't burn.
حسناً، من الناحية الفنية، فإن الشواية نفسها لا تحترق.
The meat would burn the second you place it on the grill.
سيحترق اللحم بمجرد وضعه على الشواية.
You're talking about meat burning?
هل تتحدث عن احتراق اللحم؟
That's what people mean when they say they're burning the grill.
هذا ما يقصده الناس عندما يقولون إنهم يحرقون الشواية.
Well, that's insider lingo for people who work at barbecue restaurants.
حسناً، هذه لغة داخلية يستخدمها العاملون في مطاعم الشواء.
My mom also refers to it as "burning the grill."
كما أن والدتي تشير إلى ذلك بعبارة "حرق الشواية".
Well, my mom doesn't.
حسناً، أمي لا تفعل ذلك.
- For someone who knows meat-- - There!
- لشخص يعرف اللحوم - ها هو ذا!
Get grilling.
هيا بنا نشوي.
Uh, no.
لا، لا.
It's too soon for the meat. Can't put it on a lukewarm grill.
الوقت مبكر جدًا لطهي اللحم. لا يمكن وضعه على شواية فاترة.
That would ruin the flavor. You gotta wait.
هذا سيفسد الطعم. عليك الانتظار.
Shall we maybe converse while the grill is heating up?
هل نتبادل أطراف الحديث بينما يسخن الشواية؟
Gun-woo, just speak naturally for once.
غون وو، تحدث بشكل طبيعي ولو لمرة واحدة.
Uh, so are you and Mr. Choi related?
أه، هل أنت والسيد تشوي أقارب؟
Huh? Well, that came out of left field.
هاه؟ حسناً، هذا أمر غير متوقع تماماً.
I've wanted to know too.
أردت أن أعرف ذلك أيضاً.
Since the very beginning, Juju.
منذ البداية، جوجو.
Well…
حسنًا…
…long story short…
باختصار شديد...
I was diagnosed with spinal cancer when I was eight.
تم تشخيص إصابتي بسرطان العمود الفقري عندما كنت في الثامنة من عمري.
I was cured by the time I was ten,
شفيت تماماً عندما بلغت العاشرة من عمري.
but then… my dad died.
لكن بعد ذلك... توفي والدي.
So I was sent to an orphanage,
لذلك تم إرسالي إلى دار للأيتام.
I hated it so much that I ran away.
كرهت ذلك بشدة لدرجة أنني هربت.
I used to get so hungry, you know,
كنت أشعر بجوع شديد، كما تعلم.
that I ate leftover jjajangmyeon that people left on their doorstep.
أنني أكلت بقايا جاجانغميون التي تركها الناس على عتبة بابهم.
I also worked at bars with other runaway kids,
عملتُ أيضاً في حانات مع أطفال هاربين آخرين،
but I couldn't do it anymore.
لكنني لم أعد أستطيع فعل ذلك.
So I returned to the orphanage.
لذا عدت إلى دار الأيتام.
But I was then dragged off to a different orphanage when I was 17.
لكن بعد ذلك تم اقتيادي إلى دار أيتام أخرى عندما كنت في السابعة عشرة من عمري.
And Grandpa happened to be the owner there.
وكان جدي هو المالك هناك.
- You mean Mr. Choi? - Yes.
- هل تقصد السيد تشوي؟ - نعم.
He said he built an orphanage because he wanted to do something good.
قال إنه بنى دارًا للأيتام لأنه أراد أن يفعل شيئًا جيدًا.
He was really nice to me in particular.
لقد كان لطيفاً جداً معي على وجه الخصوص.
So at first, I thought he might be a pervert, but…
في البداية، ظننت أنه قد يكون منحرفاً، لكن...
I came to know as time passed…
عرفت ذلك مع مرور الوقت...
that he was being sincere.
أنه كان صادقاً.
Grandpa paid for me to learn everything I know now.
لقد دفع لي جدي تكاليف تعلم كل ما أعرفه الآن.
because I didn't have the money.
لأنني لم أكن أملك المال.
I learned kendo, how to ride a motorcycle.
تعلمت الكيندو، وكيفية قيادة الدراجة النارية.
I could tell immediately that Mr. Choi is really a nice person.
استطعت أن أدرك على الفور أن السيد تشوي شخص لطيف حقاً.
Since middle school,
منذ المرحلة الإعدادية،
I've been working part-time jobs to pay off my dad's debt.
أعمل في وظائف بدوام جزئي لسداد ديون والدي.
But when our debt got to 100 million won,
لكن عندما وصل ديننا إلى 100 مليون وون،
I suddenly felt totally helpless.
شعرت فجأة بالعجز التام.
So I know how scary a hundred million won can be.
لذا فأنا أعرف مدى رعب مبلغ مئة مليون وون.
And when Mr. Choi gave me that money, telling me to pay off my debts,
وعندما أعطاني السيد تشوي ذلك المال، وطلب مني سداد ديوني،
I thought to myself,
فكرت في نفسي،
I have to make sure to protect this man at all costs.
يجب عليّ التأكد من حماية هذا الرجل بأي ثمن.
Grandpa told me that in order to judge someone's character,
قال لي جدي إنه لكي نحكم على شخصية شخص ما،
one should open up your heart.
ينبغي للمرء أن يفتح قلبه.
That people with character will see your sincerity
أن يرى أصحاب الأخلاق الحميدة صدقك
and return it in kind,
وأعدها بالمثل،
and those who lack depth will try to use that against you.
وأولئك الذين يفتقرون إلى العمق سيحاولون استغلال ذلك ضدك.
- Agreed. - You're a nice person, Gun-woo.
- موافق. - أنت شخص لطيف يا غون وو.
Thanks. Two things I'm good at are being nice and being diligent.
شكراً. هناك شيئان أجيدهما: أن أكون لطيفاً وأن أكون مجتهداً.
- I think we can start grilling now. - Mm-hm.
- أعتقد أننا نستطيع البدء بالشواء الآن. - هممم.
Ah!
آه!
- Ah, perfect timing. Very nice. - You're getting pretty good at this.
- آه، توقيت مثالي. جميل جداً. - أنت تتحسن كثيراً في هذا.
Well, I mean, I learned from the best, right?
حسنًا، أعني أنني تعلمت من الأفضل، أليس كذلك؟
Wow, I'm feeling so left out all of a sudden.
يا إلهي، أشعر فجأةً بأنني مستبعد تماماً.
Sheesh, never mind.
يا إلهي، لا يهم.
Hurry up and flip it.
أسرع واقلبها.
- I can't do that yet. - You gotta trust him. He's good at this.
- لا أستطيع فعل ذلك بعد. - عليك أن تثق به. إنه بارع في هذا.
Sorry, I didn't know he was the grill master.
معذرةً، لم أكن أعلم أنه خبير الشواء.
You will soon.
سوف تفعل ذلك قريباً.
Smells amazing!
رائحته رائعة!
Oh!
أوه!
Let's clean out the buffet.
هيا بنا ننظف البوفيه.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
- When are those stitches coming off? - Tomorrow morning.
- متى ستتم إزالة تلك الغرز؟ - صباح الغد.
Does it hurt?
هل يؤلمك؟
Not too bad.
ليس سيئاً للغاية.
- I asked for mine hot. - You're supposed to take your coffee cold.
طلبتُ قهوتي ساخنة. - من المفترض أن تشرب قهوتك باردة.
Seriously? Come on.
هل أنت جاد؟ هيا.
- Hyeon-ju. - Yeah?
- هيون جو. - نعم؟
Yang Jae-myeong knows where the bookstore is.
يعرف يانغ جاي ميونغ مكان المكتبة.
Shouldn't we do something about it?
ألا ينبغي علينا أن نفعل شيئاً حيال ذلك؟
I'll talk it over with Grandpa.
سأناقش الأمر مع جدي.
You should ask him soon. We don't have time.
يجب أن تسأله قريباً. ليس لدينا وقت.
Okay.
تمام.
Ms. Lee.
السيدة لي.
The lobby is a hotel's first impression.
تُعتبر ردهة الفندق الانطباع الأول الذي يتركه الفندق.
I want us to impress our international guests
أريد أن نثير إعجاب ضيوفنا الدوليين
with the most beautiful, stunning Korean experience
مع أجمل وأروع تجربة كورية
they've ever encountered.
لم يسبق لهم أن واجهوا مثله.
Something they've never experienced before.
شيء لم يسبق لهم تجربته من قبل.
That kind of thing.
هذا النوع من الأشياء.
Yes, I understand.
نعم، أفهم.
TEAM LEADER LEE SO-HYEON
قائد الفريق لي سو هيون
Anyway, I look forward to hearing your brilliant ideas.
على أي حال، أتطلع إلى سماع أفكارك الرائعة.
See you tomorrow morning.
أراك غداً صباحاً.
Our casino will be on the top floor of that hotel.
سيكون الكازينو الخاص بنا في الطابق العلوي من ذلك الفندق.
My goal is a hundred billion in annual revenue.
هدفي هو تحقيق إيرادات سنوية قدرها مئة مليار.
There are a lot of people itching for a fix
هناك الكثير من الناس الذين يتوقون إلى حل.
now that gambling in Macau has been blocked off due to COVID.
الآن وقد تم حظر المقامرة في ماكاو بسبب كوفيد-19.
We'll secretly book them a suite every week and let them have fun
سنحجز لهم جناحًا سرًا كل أسبوع وندعهم يستمتعون.
while secretly catching their gambling on camera.
بينما كانوا يلتقطون صوراً لهم وهم يمارسون القمار سراً.
Afterward, once we have enough cash,
وبعد ذلك، بمجرد أن يتوفر لدينا ما يكفي من المال،
Jang-do will make sure to hand over to the police
سيحرص جانغ دو على تسليمها للشرطة
all evidence of gambling.
جميع الأدلة على المقامرة.
When the hotel is ruined and worth nothing,
عندما يصبح الفندق مدمراً ولا قيمة له،
we'll swoop in and take over the whole thing.
سننقضّ ونسيطر على كل شيء.
We need to be ready to spend a hundred billion
علينا أن نكون مستعدين لإنفاق مئة مليار
by the time Jang-do returns with dirt on Director Hong.
بحلول وقت عودة جانغ دو، يكون لديه معلومات محرجة عن المدير هونغ.
We're 50 billion short, right?
نحن نعاني من نقص قدره 50 مليار، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
Now it's time to collect on everything.
حان الآن وقت تحصيل كل شيء.
Sell off anything that's of any value.
قم ببيع أي شيء ذي قيمة.
Coming through!
قادمون!
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Yes, that car you mentioned before just came in.
نعم، تلك السيارة التي ذكرتها سابقاً وصلت للتو.
Cool.
رائع.
I'll be right back, sir.
سأعود حالاً يا سيدي.
What the…
يا إلهي...
CAR WASH EXIT NO PARKING
مخرج مغسلة السيارات، ممنوع الوقوف
Hello!
مرحبًا!
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
All right, keep him down.
حسناً، أبقوه أرضاً.
Look at him!
انظر إليه!
You want more, huh?
تريد المزيد، أليس كذلك؟
Grab him.
أمسك به.
Hey, strip him down.
هيا، انزع عنه ملابسه.
Ah.
آه.
- He's this way. - Is he in there now?
- إنه من هنا. - هل هو بالداخل الآن؟
- Yes. - Thank you for your hard work.
- نعم. - شكراً لك على عملك الجاد.
- You can count it. - Thank you, sir.
- يمكنك عدّها. - شكراً لك سيدي.
Look at him.
انظر إليه.
Hey. Hey, shh.
مهلاً. مهلاً، اصمت.
Whoa! You boys sure did a number on him.
يا إلهي! لقد ألحقتم به ضرراً بالغاً يا أولاد.
- Hello, sir!
- مرحباً سيدي!
I'm so cold.
أشعر ببرد شديد.
Can I please have something to wear? Please.
هل يمكنني الحصول على شيء أرتديه من فضلك؟
God, I'm… I'm sorry, sir.
يا إلهي، أنا... أنا آسف يا سيدي.
Hi there.
أهلاً.
You…
أنت…
You, it's you, isn't it? Fuck.
أنتَ، أنتَ هو، أليس كذلك؟ تباً.
Motherfucker!
يا ابن العاهرة!
Jesus, not too long ago, you were acting like hot shit.
يا يسوع، قبل فترة ليست طويلة، كنت تتصرف بشكل رائع للغاية.
Prick.
وخزة.
So,
لذا،
you really shouldn't have fucked around with him.
كان عليك ألا تعبث معه.
Did you think he would get scared
هل ظننت أنه سيخاف؟
and apologize to you or something just because your cousin's a cop? Huh?
وهل تعتذر لي أو شيء من هذا القبيل لمجرد أن ابن عمك شرطي؟ هاه؟
Listen, let me teach you a little lesson.
اسمع، دعني أعلمك درساً صغيراً.
Wild animals bite back if you hit them.
الحيوانات البرية تعض إذا ضربتها.
It doesn't matter how much stronger or weaker you are than them.
لا يهم كم أنت أقوى أو أضعف منهم.
They just bite back.
إنهم يردون بالمثل.
Now then.
والآن.
Strip down.
انزع ملابسك.
What?
ماذا؟
Come on, take everything off, including your underwear.
هيا، اخلع كل شيء، بما في ذلك ملابسك الداخلية.
No, I get it now. Please, just this once.
لا، فهمت الآن. أرجوك، هذه المرة فقط.
- Ugh. - I'm sorry.
- أوه. - أنا آسف.
I really don't know what this is about, but I'm really sorry.
لا أعرف حقاً ما هو موضوع هذا الأمر، لكنني آسف حقاً.
Hey, In-beom.
مرحباً، إن-بيوم.
Please, just this once.
أرجوك، هذه المرة فقط.
Wrap it up.
اختتم الأمر.
Are you stripping or not?
هل تقومين بالتعري أم لا؟
Don't kill me.
لا تقتلني.
I guess you're still thirsty.
أظن أنك ما زلت تشعر بالعطش.
- Oh! - What's it gonna be?
- أوه! - ماذا سيكون؟
- Well… - I'll strip down! I'll strip down!
- حسنًا... - سأخلع ملابسي! سأخلع ملابسي!
Good call.
قرار صائب.
Now then, Director Hong, without further ado,
والآن، أيها المخرج هونغ، دون مزيد من الإطالة،
let's see you strip.
هيا نراك تتعرى.
I GOT SOMETHING BIG
لقد حصلت على شيء كبير
All right, that's enough.
حسناً، هذا يكفي.
Yes.
نعم.
Uh, Mr. Choi,
آه، سيد تشوي،
the Kim Myeong-gil we know is indeed the CEO of Smile Capital.
إن كيم ميونغ غيل الذي نعرفه هو بالفعل الرئيس التنفيذي لشركة سمايل كابيتال.
Yes, I understand.
نعم، أفهم.
I'm coming to pick you up. I'll be there soon, sir.
سآتي لأخذك. سأكون هناك قريباً يا سيدي.
Yes.
نعم.
I apologize for my sudden decision.
أعتذر عن قراري المفاجئ.
Recently, I've gone through something very difficult for me.
لقد مررت مؤخراً بشيء صعب للغاية بالنسبة لي.
And I came to this conclusion after thinking things over,
وتوصلت إلى هذا الاستنتاج بعد التفكير ملياً في الأمر.
so I hope you'll understand.
لذا آمل أن تتفهموا ذلك.
Our company will be terminated by the end of the month.
سيتم إنهاء خدمات شركتنا بنهاية الشهر.
I will be wiring you
سأقوم بتحويل المبلغ إليك
all of your salary as well as your severance pay.
راتبك بالكامل بالإضافة إلى مكافأة نهاية الخدمة.
Thanks for everything.
شكراً على كل شيء.
Sir, what about… all of our money that's out there right now?
سيدي، ماذا عن... كل أموالنا الموجودة هناك الآن؟
I'm gonna take care of it.
سأتولى الأمر.
Papa!
بابا!
- Yes. - This is Oh In-muk in security, sir.
- نعم. - هذا أوه إن-موك من قسم الأمن، سيدي.
Some robbers have broken into your office.
اقتحم بعض اللصوص مكتبك.
How many?
كم عدد؟
I think there are two.
أعتقد أن هناك اثنين.
Hey!
يا!
What's taking you so long?
ما الذي يؤخرك كل هذا الوقت؟
This model normally comes with a six-digit combination.
يأتي هذا الطراز عادةً برمز مكون من ستة أرقام.
This one has eight.
هذا واحد فيه ثمانية.
I think they modified it.
أعتقد أنهم قاموا بتعديله.
- What does that mean? - Gonna need more time.
- ماذا يعني ذلك؟ - سأحتاج إلى مزيد من الوقت.
Hurry it up.
أسرعوا.
Got it!
فهمتها!
Out of the way.
ابتعد عن الطريق.
PRIVATE LOAN STANDARD AGREEMENT
اتفاقية قرض خاص قياسية
These promissory notes are worth a billion won a pop.
تبلغ قيمة كل سند إذني مليار وون.
Fuck!
اللعنة!
No one has come out. I also held the elevator here.
لم يخرج أحد. لقد أوقفت المصعد هنا أيضاً.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Uh, shall I accompany you?
أه، هل أرافقك؟
Oh, no. I'll be fine. Thank you very much.
لا، سأكون بخير. شكراً جزيلاً لك.
Uh, let me just borrow this.
حسنًا، دعني أستعير هذا.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
How did you get in?
كيف دخلت؟
Who sent you?
من أرسلك؟
Fuck.
اللعنة.
Sir, are you okay?
سيدي، هل أنت بخير؟
Kill that fucker!
اقتل ذلك الوغد!
It's okay, Beom. Huh?
لا بأس يا بوم. هاه؟
- Snap out of it. You're okay. - Okay.
- اهدأ. أنت بخير. - حسناً.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
- Kang In-beom! - Yes, sir!
- كانغ إن-بيوم! - نعم سيدي!
We don't have time.
ليس لدينا وقت.
Take all the money in the safe and head down first, okay?
خذ كل الأموال الموجودة في الخزنة وانزل أولاً، حسناً؟
Calm down. Calm down.
اهدأ. اهدأ.
Huh?
هاه؟
Sir!
سيد!
He's not there!
إنه ليس هناك!
- Just go downstairs. - Yes, sir.
- انزل إلى الطابق السفلي. - حاضر سيدي.
- Mr. Choi. - Hm?
- السيد تشوي. - همم؟
Have you thought about it yet?
هل فكرت في الأمر بعد؟
What's the problem?
ما المشكلة؟
Let's avoid Yang Jae-myeong.
دعونا نتجنب يانغ جاي ميونغ.
Why?
لماذا؟
Those people also resort to killing.
يلجأ هؤلاء الأشخاص أيضاً إلى القتل.
I want to move the bookstore as well.
أريد نقل المكتبة أيضاً.
Why?
لماذا؟
Hyeon-ju.
هيون جو.
Look at me.
انظر إليَّ.
I am old and tired.
أنا عجوز ومتعب.
There's no strength or courage left in me
لم يتبق في داخلي أي قوة أو شجاعة
to fight them.
لمحاربتهم.
I just want to live my remaining days in peace,
كل ما أريده هو أن أعيش أيامي المتبقية بسلام.
teaching you the things I want to teach you,
سأعلمك الأشياء التي أريد أن أعلمك إياها،
and giving you all the things that…
وتقديم كل الأشياء التي...
that I want to leave to you once I'm not here anymore.
أريد أن أترك لك ذلك عندما أرحل عن هذه الدنيا.
That is the only thing I want right now.
هذا هو الشيء الوحيد الذي أريده الآن.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
هل تفهم ما أقوله؟
Good.
جيد.
And thank you.
وشكراً لكم.
Remember, the value of gold rises
تذكر، قيمة الذهب ترتفع
every single time people lose confidence in fiat currency.
في كل مرة يفقد فيها الناس ثقتهم بالعملات الورقية.
You gotta your slush fund in gold.
يجب أن يكون لديك صندوق أسود من الذهب.
Besides, if you melt the gold down and mix it with other gold,
إضافة إلى ذلك، إذا قمت بصهر الذهب وخلطه مع ذهب آخر،
it launders itself.
إنها تغسل نفسها بنفسها.
That was the very first thing I learned when I worked for Choi.
كان ذلك أول شيء تعلمته عندما عملت لدى تشوي.
Failing to get my hands on his hidden gold…
فشلت في الحصول على ذهبه المخفي...
is something that I still regret.
إنه أمر ما زلت أشعر بالندم عليه.
That old stupid fuck.
ذلك الأحمق العجوز.
He suddenly grows a conscience and closes down the damn company.
فجأةً، استيقظ ضميره وأغلق الشركة اللعينة.
- Beom. - Yes, sir.
- بيوم. - نعم سيدي.
Get in here.
ادخل إلى هنا.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
It's amazing.
إنه لأمر مذهل.
Each bar is worth 500 million.
تبلغ قيمة كل قطعة 500 مليون.
If our business in Korea goes south,
إذا ساءت أعمالنا في كوريا،
you and I will take all this gold and go to Vietnam.
سنأخذ أنا وأنت كل هذا الذهب ونذهب إلى فيتنام.
Huh?
هاه؟
We can hide there.
يمكننا الاختباء هناك.
I planted someone in the Vietnamese government.
لقد زرعت شخصاً في الحكومة الفيتنامية.
Thanks to this,
بفضل هذا،
we should be able to live like kings for the rest of our days.
ينبغي أن نكون قادرين على العيش كالملوك لبقية أيامنا.
Thank you, sir. I…
شكراً لك سيدي. أنا…
You're a brother to me.
أنت بمثابة أخي.
I would do anything for you.
سأفعل أي شيء من أجلك.
Beom, listen.
بيوم، استمع.
Out here, you are all I've got.
هنا، أنت كل ما أملك.
You know that, right?
أنت تعلم ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
Mm-hm.
ممم.
Come on.
تعال.
It's the best stir-fried spicy pork in the world.
إنه أفضل لحم خنزير مقلي حار في العالم.
- It's that good? - Yeah.
- هل هو جيد لهذه الدرجة؟ - نعم.
Auntie? Auntie!
خالتي؟ خالتي!
Auntie. Auntie.
خالتي. خالتي.
It's okay. It's okay. It's me, Woo-jin.
لا بأس. لا بأس. أنا وو جين.
Oh God, Woo-jin. Woo-jin, Woo-jin.
يا إلهي، وو جين. وو جين، وو جين.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
I… I took out a private loan.
لقد... لقد حصلت على قرض خاص.
They told me to pay them back.
طلبوا مني أن أسدد لهم المبلغ.
I told them I had no money because I didn't get any customers today.
أخبرتهم أنني لا أملك نقوداً لأنني لم أحصل على أي زبائن اليوم.
And they smashed everything.
وحطموا كل شيء.
God, I'm scared. I'm so scared.
يا إلهي، أنا خائف. أنا خائف جداً.
What do I do?
ماذا أفعل؟
How is she supposed to operate her business if you smash it up?
كيف يُفترض بها أن تدير عملها إذا دمرته؟
How do you expect her to pay you back now?
كيف تتوقع منها أن تسدد لك دينك الآن؟
She wasn't paying. What should I do?
لم تكن تدفع. ماذا أفعل؟
You should ease up on them. Everyone's having a tough time.
يجب أن تخفف عنهم. الجميع يمر بوقت عصيب.
And how am I supposed to make a living?
وكيف يُفترض بي أن أكسب رزقي؟
You know what, why don't you pay for her?
أتعرف ماذا؟ لماذا لا تدفع أنت ثمنها؟
Come on, you know I don't have the money for that.
هيا، أنت تعلم أنني لا أملك المال لذلك.
Then just shut your goddamn mouth.
إذن، أغلق فمك اللعين.
And mind your own fucking business.
واهتم بشؤونك الخاصة.
- Got it? - Fine.
- فهمت؟ - حسناً.
It's Im.
إنه أنا.
I worked with him back in the day.
لقد عملت معه في الماضي.
Apparently, he just got conned by someone he lent 500 million to.
على ما يبدو، فقد تعرض للاحتيال من قبل شخص أقرضه 500 مليون.
- Is Yang Jae-myeong involved? - I don't know.
- هل يانغ جاي ميونغ متورط؟ - لا أعرف.
I didn't ask for the details.
لم أطلب التفاصيل.
But it was a homeless person's ID that they used to open a fake account.
لكنهم استخدموا هوية شخص بلا مأوى لفتح حساب مزيف.
Identical MO.
آلية عمل متطابقة.
It's him.
إنه هو.
I say we should catch him.
أقول إنه يجب علينا القبض عليه.
I can't just stand by and do nothing about it.
لا يمكنني أن أقف مكتوف الأيدي ولا أفعل شيئاً حيال ذلك.
Grandpa told us to lie low.
قال لنا جدي أن نلتزم الصمت.
That they're really dangerous.
إنهم خطرون حقاً.
But I think it's wrong to do nothing after seeing all that.
لكنني أعتقد أنه من الخطأ عدم القيام بأي شيء بعد رؤية كل ذلك.
What if I call him back and tip him off about Yang Jae-myeong,
ماذا لو اتصلت به مجدداً وأخبرته عن يانغ جاي ميونغ؟
so he can catch him himself.
حتى يتمكن من الإمساك به بنفسه.
If the goal is to capture him, we should do it.
إذا كان الهدف هو القبض عليه، فعلينا أن نفعل ذلك.
Maybe we could make some money.
ربما نستطيع جني بعض المال.
If we do make money from this, can I use it to help out Auntie?
إذا ربحنا مالاً من هذا، فهل يمكنني استخدامه لمساعدة عمتي؟
If we do, we'll split it evenly. Feel free to use it however you see fit.
إذا فعلنا ذلك، فسوف نقسمها بالتساوي. لا تتردد في استخدامها بالطريقة التي تراها مناسبة.
- Cool. - Then I want to help her too.
- رائع. - إذن أريد مساعدتها أيضاً.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
- Come on over. - No.
- تعال إلى هنا. - لا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
All in.
الكل في الكل.
Sir, you should look at this.
سيدي، يجب أن تنظر في هذا.
That car over there.
تلك السيارة هناك.
They cut the engine, but no one's getting out.
قاموا بإيقاف المحرك، لكن لا أحد يستطيع الخروج.
- Hey, get ready. - Yes, sir.
- هيا، استعد. - حاضر سيدي.
Hey, check your phone.
يا رجل، تفقد هاتفك.
- Okay, okay.
- نعم سيدي. - حسناً، حسناً.
Hey, sir, they're here.
أهلاً سيدي، لقد وصلوا.
In exactly two hours, make your move.
في غضون ساعتين بالضبط، تحرك.
They're here.
إنهم هنا.
Let's go. Let's go.
هيا بنا. هيا بنا.
You're gonna die today, you dumb fucks.
ستموتون اليوم أيها الأغبياء.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Come down now.
انزل الآن.
Come out!
يخرج!
Hey, you fuckers, I know you're there, so hurry up and show yourselves.
يا أيها الأوغاد، أعرف أنكم هنا، لذا أسرعوا وأظهروا أنفسكم.
Come out, assholes! What is this, hide-and-seek?
اخرجوا أيها الأوغاد! ما هذا، لعبة الغميضة؟
Motherfuckers.
يا أبناء العاهرات.
Please pick up…
يرجى الاستلام…
Please.
لو سمحت.
HYEON-JU
هيون جو
- Mm? - Grandpa.
- مم؟ - جدي.
Woo-jin and Gun-woo are in danger.
وو جين وجون وو في خطر.
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
- Get a move on. - Let's go! Let's go!
- هيا بنا ! - هيا بنا!
You sons of bitches!
يا أبناء العاهرات!
- Let's get 'em. - Fuck.
- هيا بنا نهزمهم. - اللعنة.
- Get a move on. - Go, go, go!
- أسرعوا! - انطلقوا، انطلقوا، انطلقوا!
Oh, fuck. This is insane.
يا إلهي! هذا جنون.
Hey, you sons of bitches.
يا أبناء العاهرات.